VITAL ILYUCHYK

Frontend Developer

+375444800968 wital128@tut.by

https://vwital.netlify.app https://t.me/wutalich



EDUCATION

Biologist-ecologist

Yanka Kupala State **University of Grodna** 2015 - 2019

Master's degree **Specialty "Ecology"**

Yanka Kupala State **University of Grodna** 2019 - 2020

STACK

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Webpack, Vite
- <u>TypeScript</u>
- ReactJS
- scss/sass
- Git
- Postman

LANGUAGES

- English Intermediate
- Belarussian Native
- Russian Native
- <u>Ukrainian</u> Intermediate

PROFILE

Sociable, non-conflict person, attentive to details. I have critical thinking, flexibility, and am ready to work productively and develop.

I have no experience in IT, however, I have experience in writing projects in native HTML CSS JS, TS, ReactJS. Working with SASS/SCSS preprocessors, Webpack and Vite project builders. Website layout using Figma layout. Adaptive layout. PerfectPixel layout. Teamwork. Work on SCRUM, using Git, JIRA. Some projects can see on my website - portfolio.

CERTIFICATES

RSSchool

Stage 0

RSSchool

Stage 1-2

https://app.rs.school/certificate/2e8h22le https://app.rs.school/certificate/q4ko9gj9

EF SET

English certification https://cert.efset.org/GCEbvn

EXTRA SKILLS

- MS Oficce
- Adobe Photoshop
- Vegas Pro
- Notion

WORK EXPERIENCE

Comprehensive school

2020 - 2023

Chemistry and Biology Teacher

- Teaching high school students.
- Writing plans, working with documentation

ВИТАЛИЙ ИЛЬЮЧИК

Frontend разработчик

+375444800968

wital128@tut.by

https://vwital.netlify.app https://t.me/wutalich

ОБРАЗОВАНИЕ

Биолог - эколог

ГрГУ им. Янки Купалы 2015<u>- 2019</u>

Магистр в области экологии

ГрГУ им. Янки Купалы 2019 - 2020

CTEK

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Webpack, Vite
- <u>TypeScript</u>
- ReactJS
- scss/sass
- Git
- Postman

ЯЗЫКИ

- Английский Средний
- Беларусский Носитель
- Русский Носитель
- Украинский Средний

PROFILE

<u>Коммуникабельный, неконфликтный человек, внимательный к</u> деталям. Обладаю критическим мышлением, гибкостью, готов продуктивно работать и развиваться.

У меня нет опыта работы в IT, однако есть опыт написания проектов на нативном HTML CSS JS, TS, ReactJS. Работа с препроцессорами SASS/SCSS, сборщиками проектов Webpack и Vite. Верстка сайта с использованием макетов Figma. Адаптивная верстка. Верстка PerfectPixel. Командная работа. Работа по SCRUM, используя Git, JIRA. Некоторые проекты находятся на моем сайте - портфолио.

СЕРТИФИКАТЫ

RSSchool

Stage 1-2

RSSchool

Stage 0

https://app.rs.school/certificate/2e8h22le https://app.rs.school/certificate/q4ko9gj9

EF SET

English certification https://cert.efset.org/GCEbvn

<u>ДОПОЛНИТЕЛЬНЫЕ НАВЫКИ</u>

- MS Oficce
- Adobe Photoshop
- Vegas Pro
- Notion

ОПЫТ РАБОТЫ

Общеобразовательная школа

2020 - 2023

Учитель химии и биологии

- Обучение учащихся старших классов.
- Составление планов, работа с документацией.